a-msystems.com 2003-06-01

# Privacy Statement

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.a-msystems.com. 

#### Information Collection and Use

A-M Systems, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. A-M Systems, Inc. collects and uses information from our customers in several ways, including the processing of purchase orders, return authorizations, mailing list subscriptions, requests for literature, and website usage. 

#### Information Requests and Order Processing

Our collection of your personal information is to facilitate the delivery of product information and purchases. Contact information (i.e., name, address, account number), financial information (i.e. credit card number, expiration date, purchase order number) and shipping instructions may be collected and retained.  This includes purchase history information as required by the United States Food and Drug Administration for tracking of regulated medical devices. 

#### Mailing List

We maintain a mailing list of our customers.  We provide you with the opportunity to received Product Catalogs, Sale Flyers, and other product information in print or electronic formats.  We also provide you with the ability to stop subscriptions to this information.

However, you may still receive literature from us occasionally when we rent or purchase mailing lists from other organizations.  This is always done within the contract provisions provided by the mailing list owner, and may not provide us with the ability to combine a rented list with the user preferences in our mailing list database. 

#### Passwords

We ask you to select a password to protect your personal information when you request information or place an order with us. The password will allow you to update this information. Our Customer Service Representatives will not ask you for your password over the telephone or in writing. For your own protection, we urge you not share your password with anyone. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password. 

#### EMail-A-Friend

If you elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send this person a one-time email containing the information you wish to send.  The friend will not be entered as an active member of our mailing list as a result of this process. 

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive containing an temporary identification number used to track the products and services you place in your shopping cart. A cookie can never tell us any personally identifiable information you have not already given us. If you reject our cookie, some services of our site will be unavailable. Cookies can also enable us to track the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

#### Log Files

We use log files containing computer IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the website, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. For your protection, we also record you computer's IP address when you log in, change personal information, or make a purchase, in order to guard your security by facilitating any investigation of  unusual user activity. 

#### Sharing

We do not share customer information with third parties for marketing purposes.

We use outside shipping companies to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill credit card transactions for goods and services. 

#### Links

Our web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other sites.  This privacy statement applies to information collected at www.a-msystems.com. 

#### Surveys

From time-to-time our site may request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information and/or demographic information, and participation may require registration with the website. 

#### Security

A-M Systems, Inc. takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, it is protected both online and off-line. Sensitive information submitted to our website is encrypted and protected with SSL, which is the best encryption software available today. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer indicates that all data is being encrypted for your protection. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect this information offline. All of our users’ information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are allowed access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, the servers which store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

#### Supplementation of Information

In order for us to fulfill our obligation to our customers, occasionally it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from third party sources. For example, with specific permission, we may conduct a credit check in conjunction with a purchase order. 

#### Updating Personal Information & Opt-out

When your personally identifiable information changes, we encourage you to log in to our website by clicking 'My Account' where you will be given an opportunity to update any personal information on record with us. You are always given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your information used for any purpose by choosing to unsubscribe from our mailing list. Your contact information will be retained in our mailing list to ensure that you are not added back to the list at a later time without your permission. 

#### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post an updated privacy statement here so you are always aware of our current policy. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy in effect when the information was collected. If at any point we desire to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated in the privacy policy at the time the information was collected, we will only do so if we first obtain your permission.
